export const verbPracticeDataHaykakan = {
  2: [
    { prompt: "Ես", answer: "եմ" },
    { prompt: "Դու", answer: "ես" },
    { prompt: "Նա", answer: "է" },
    { prompt: "Այն", answer: "է" },
    { prompt: "ենք", answer: "մենք" },
    { prompt: "ես", answer: "դու" },
    { prompt: "է", answer: "նա/այն" }
  ],
  3: [
    { prompt: "Ես", answer: "ունեմ" },
    { prompt: "Դու", answer: "ունես" },
    { prompt: "Նա", answer: "ունի" },
    { prompt: "Այն", answer: "ունի" },
    { prompt: "ունենամ", answer: "ես/դու/նա/այն" }
  ]
};
